Yeah.
Breathing
have
is that people have.
This is
Yeah.
Thank you.
Thinking about
Oh, Okay.
Yeah,
Yeah.
Uh oh.
Spotted?
Oh,
yeah.
Oh, oh,
right.
All right.
Yes.
You know
Oh,
oh!
Oh.
Okay.
Right.
What city?
Yeah.
Yeah,
E.
Okay.
Oh,
I can't believe
Good luck.
No.
All right.
Yeah.
More.
No,
my focus is picking up some kind of signal.
Maybe I could scan it
right?
Mhm.
Read.
I watch her.
I hitting this component deals greater damage to the machine.
Mhm.
Pretty.
Right?
All right.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah, yeah,
right.
E anymore.
No,
Joe,
right?
Yeah.
Mhm.
Yes.
Yeah.
Mhm.
Uh huh.
No.
Uh, all right, it comes.
Yeah.
Oh,
thank you.
Uh huh.
Yeah,
Yeah.
I must be closing in on the signal.
Okay.
Yeah,
no problem.
It's
Yeah.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
It's
the culture.
What's that?
Mm.
You're from inside the embrace.
So you've never seen one?
A cauldron is a sort of door.
I guess.
No one knows what lies beyond
a cauldron.
There's gotta be a way in somehow.
Quite a door.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Shoot
the metal.
The light.
It's like this entire place is part of some huge machine.
But who made it?
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
Oh,
and stuff
that thing looks like a triangular pipe.
What's the for?
Uh huh.
That might give me some cover if I need it.
We can.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yes.
Those things are moving components around.
E wonder where
a few years.
No.
Trust me.
Yeah,
yeah,
Yeah.
Okay.
Well,
okay.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah,
a thing near the gap.
What does it do?
Okay,
Thank you.
Oh, very helpful.
This
mhm.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
Yes,
right.
That's fine.
Mhm.
So it looks like those flying machines milk components around might be able to take the song.
Might regret this,
you know?
Yes.
That's the heart of it all.
It's got
Do I get inside?
I've got a faras This thing will take me.
She's just a kid.
Starting
Mhm.
Okay.
Whoa.
Yeah.
Okay.
I don't agree.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
Okay.
Seven.
Yeah,
Yeah.
Do you think that
Okay,
you're down.
Others haven't noticed.
Three.
Okay,
that's the question.
That's
thank you.
Yeah.
Uh huh.
What?
Come on,
E.
My father.
Yeah,
Shell Walker.
Great holders.
Destroying this component will detach the cargo container.
Lightning gun destroying this component disables the range.
Shock attacks Power generator Destroying the power generator disables all shock attacks the shield and triggers an explosion Shocking Anything in the area shield pla Destroying this component disables the energy shield.
Whoa,
Thank you.
Okay.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Okay.
Yes.
All right.
She
thank you.
You look a course
back to work,
right?
Thank you.
Yeah.
All right.
Okay.
Yeah.
The doctor?
Today?
Yeah.
Home.
You know.
Mhm.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
Okay.
Have
Yeah.
Okay.
Six.
Almost.
To the heart.
Okay.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
Need them soon enough?
Uh huh.
Okay.
Yeah.
Was the first one?
Yeah,
man.
Nice is how machines were made.
Moving out of flight.
There are signals coming from all over the place.
What,
All the time.
Watch.
Yeah,
thanks.
Okay.
Yeah.
Fight
What?
Mhm.
Mr.
Campbell?
Yeah.
What?
No.
Yeah,
that's so interesting.
Yeah.
What?
Okay.
Yeah, yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
The problem.
Yeah.
All right.
Okay.
Yeah.
Thank you for
There you go.
Yeah.
Okay.
Hungry?
It's
breathe.
Really?
From me.
Yeah.
Chicken back.
Okay.
Yeah, we're ready to go.
Yeah,
yeah,
right.
okay?
Yeah.
That machines making, making a ticket with this stuff.
You know.
Uh huh.
Sure.
One more time.
Go.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Sure.
Yeah.
Oh,
thanks.
How about that?
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah.
Oh,
Across.
Yeah.
Oh,
yeah.
Have a
Yeah,
I've got a Yeah.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Just
not really.
Uh huh.
Yeah.
Sure.
Oh,
okay.
Yeah.
Thank you,
E.
I
don't know
what
Yeah.
Strangled.
Oh,
no.
Yeah.
Okay.
No.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Okay.
Information about different machines.
This will help me override them.
Some machines are built in places like this.
Why?
Summary Active Production, Oversight analysis.
Additive manufacturer type alert.
Intrusion source.
External active countermeasure phase.
Shift alert.
Intrusion denied.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Let me.
Yeah.
No, really?
Okay.